honsyuan.com 2019-06-20

# Privacy Policy

honsyuan.com respects your privacy and makes your online safety our top priority. In order to keep you updated, offer you a wide range of great products as well as give you the most effective customer service, we log information from your time on our site. 

We take your privacy and security very seriously and would like to explain the policies we have in place to protect your personal information. 

Access to this Personal Information is only available to certain staff members and will be safeguarded at all times. We use industry standard methods such as data encryption to protect your data where legally required or as needed for your safety and protection, giving you a secure environment to browse whilst reducing the risk of unauthorized access. 

Your Personal Information is secured in a protected physical environment as well as via secured technical methods as well. Personal information or backup information is not authorized at any time to leave the premises without prior permission. 

Information that may be collected: your registered email, password, gender, shipping and billing address(es), phone number, email address, credit/Debit or other card number, the date and time, browser and operating system information, the URL you request. 

Additionally, we may enquire about your country of residence and/or your organization?s country of operation, so that we may comply with relevant laws and regulations. This information is needed for billing, order processing and internal marketing promotions and helps us to understand and communicate with you regarding orders you have made on our site. 

If you are a member of our drop shipping or other marketing affiliate, we may collect information such as: your telephone number, your website, MSN, your reviews and testimonials and other such relevant information. 

**Use of Information:**

We only use your personal information to manage your orders and offer you a greater and more detailed customer service support. We do not under any circumstances sell or rent your data to any other party for any reason. 

Your personal information may be used within the company to log general information about visits to this site to help improve site content and display/layout, increase our outreach and promote our products and services. 

We will use your personal information to correspond with you directly regarding our site and the orders that you have placed through our site. Every customer must use a relevant and correct email address to enable appropriate correspondence with honsyuan.com relating to orders placed on the site. A confirmation email may be forwarded to you after registration on our site as well as service-related messages as necessary such as a temporary site suspension of service for updates or site maintenance. If you subscribe to our newsletter by registering with your email address, you may receive email alerts for products, features, special offers, contests, events of interest, and one-off marketing promotions. Such alerts may include marketing information about honsyuan.com, our subsidiaries or selected business partners. To unsubscribe from future newsletters or other promotions please follow the directions on the bottom of the email where an unsubscribe link is available or contact customer service for further instructions. 

As do other online retailers, we occasionally use third-party service providers to perform certain tasks on our behalf. Tasks include delivery of packages and credit card process payments. Other such cases where your information may be given out would be if required by law or if this company merges with or is acquired by another company. 

All information disclosed to third parties is only provided to help in the third parties provision of service. We may present information such as your shipping address, your name, email and phone number to further partners such as DHL, FEDEX, TNT, Singapore Post, EMS, China Post, HK Post, UPS and a range of other postal services in order to guarantee your order delivery. We may also use relevant customer information to evaluate the quality of the third party?s services. 

In regards to credit card number: We must provide your credit card details to appropriate financial service organizations such as credit card processors and issuers in order for us to process payments. We endeavor to protect all instances of credit card number submission for authorization with current, legal and up-to-date data encryption methods. 

If served with a court order, subpoenaed, ordered by law-enforcement officials investigating criminal activity or otherwise required by law to disclose such information, we may be legally bound to disclose certain personal information. We may also pass on personal information if we feel the need to protect our legal rights or when and if needed to enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements. We therefore may pass on certain information if we believe we are at risk of fraud, or in order to prevent fraud by users who attempt to defraud or use any other illegal means on or through our Site. 

We strictly adhere to our company policy to not sell, trade or rent your personal information to another company though it is possible that we may merge with, acquire or be acquired by another company or that we might dispose of some or all of our assets. In this situation your personal information may be passed onto the new company, subject to a Privacy Notice in effect. 

We may also share information that does not identify you or any user, such as the number of daily visitors to a particular page, or the size of an order placed on a certain date, with third parties such as advertising partners. In order to keep you up-to-date regarding which information we have logged, used and disclosed, we will notify you of any changes or updates to the Privacy Notice on this site and advise you to review the Privacy Notice at times. If you have any further questions regarding our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us anytime via the customer service contact page. 

If you wish to know more about our Privacy Policy, you can visit the Customer Service Center of our web site and contact us for more information. If you wish to talk to our customer service staff. You can also email us at zebadiah@honsyuan.com.
